exercise4weightloss.com 2016-03-14

# Privacy Policy for Exercise 4 Weight Loss

##### [Home](http://www.exercise4weightloss.com/) ›  Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to me.  I am a very private person myself, so I understand the reluctance to share certain information with people you don’t know.  

I recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information I receive and collect when you use exercise4weightloss.com, as well as some of the steps I take to safeguard information. I hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with me.

Exercise4weightloss.com strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, I am dedicated to protecting my online visitors' privacy on this website. 

## Personal Information

Exercise4weightloss.com collects personally identifiable information from the visitors to this website only on a voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a voluntary basis may include name, postal address, email address, company name and telephone number.

This information is collected if you contact me, participate in a contest or sweepstakes, and sign up to join an email list or request some other service or information from this website. 

The information collected is internally reviewed, used to improve the content of this website, notify our visitors of updates, and respond to visitor inquiries.

Once information is reviewed, it is discarded or stored in our files. If I make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information I will inform you by placing a notice on this site. 

Personal information received from any visitor will be used only for internal purposes and will not be sold or provided to third parties.

## Use of Cookies and Web Beacons

This site may use cookies to help you personalize your online experience. Cookies are identifiers that are transferred to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. 

The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize the sites pages, or register with any of this site's services, a cookie enables exercise4weightloss.com to recall your specific information on subsequent visits.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your Web browser; however, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site.

A web beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor your journey around a single website or collection of sites. They are also referred to as web bugs and are commonly used by sites that hire third-party services to monitor traffic. 

They may be used in association with cookies to understand how visitors interact with the pages and content on the pages of a web site.

This site may serve third party advertisements that use cookies and web beacons in the course of ads being served on the web site to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. No personally identifiable information you give us is provided to them for cookie or web beacon use, so they cannot personally identify you with that information on this web site.

Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is being sent. Privacy software can be used to override web beacons. Taking either of these actions shouldn't cause a problem with this site, should you so choose.

## Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act

This website is directed to adults; it is not directed to children under the age of 13. I operate this site in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, and will not knowingly collect or use personal information from anyone under 13 years of age.

## Non-Personal Information

In some cases, I may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. The site uses this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about the user base as a whole. 

The information collected is used solely for internal review and not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

## Release of Information

If exercise4weightloss.com is sold, the information I have obtained from you through your voluntary participation in this site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale in order that the service being provided to you may continue. 

In that event, you will receive notice through this website of that change in control and practices, and I will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make of us. 

## How to Correct/ Remove Information

We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal information through our website and would like that information deleted from the records or would like to update or correct that information, please use the [contact me](http://www.exercise4weightloss.com/contact.html) page.

## Updates and Effective Date

Exercise4weightloss.com reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in the privacy practices, I will indicate on this site that the privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy policy. 

I encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information I collect and how I use it.

## Agreeing the Terms

If you do not agree to exercise4weightloss.com Privacy Policy as posted here on this website, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site.

Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy.

### Monthly ezine

Free tips and recipes monthly. What do you have to lose...except some weight.....Sign up now.
